Hi, I'm Jennifer Cail.
Now that we've gotten all of our easy dirt and grease up, it's time to go in for the stubborn stains using some baking soda.
For using the baking soda, all you want to do is make a little bit of a paste so we're going to sprinkle some baking soda, it's fine, it's in lumps.
We're going to wet our sponge just a little bit and then we're going to gently pat up some you can see it's on the sponge and we're going to start scrubbing.
You can see it's taking this off really really well, you're just going to get some more a wonderful thing about baking soda.
It's incredibly cheap.
this will be the cheapest cleaning supply that you can probably find.
It's also completely environmentally friendly you don't have to worry about any toxics smells, you don't have to worry about your children getting into it.
Thank goodness you use it in baked goods all the time so you can see how that's really coming up quiet nicely.
You can use as much as you want; it does take a little bit of elbow grease getting in there.
But you can see how well it's coming up and you also don't have like chemicals smell when you using this.
If you're pregnant you don't have to worry about any of the fumes so we're just going to keep applying more and more baking soda until it all comes up.